BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 17) 6178/017
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Telephone Employees - Cleveland, OH, 1924 (Box 16, Folder 131)
- Telephone Employees - Waycross, GA, 1923 (Box 16, Folder 132)
- Telephone Employees - Brunswick, GA, 1923 (Box 16, Folder 133)
- Telephone Employees - Cincinnati, OH, 1919 (Box 16, Folder 134)
- Telephone Operators - Boston, MA, 1923-1925 (Box 16, Folder 135)
- Telephone Operators - Terre Haute, IN, 1922-1925 (Box 16, Folder 136)
- Telephone Operators - Taylorville, IL, 1924 (Box 16, Folder 137)
- Telephone Operators - Murphysboro, IL, 1923 (Box 16, Folder 138)
- Telephone Workers - Bloomington, IL, 1923-1925 (Box 16, Folder 139)
- Telephone Operators - Portland, OR, 1923 (Box 16, Folder 140)
- Telephone Operators - Lincoln, NE, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 141)
- Telephone Employees - Lynn, MA, 1923 (Box 16, Folder 142)
- United Textile Workers - Madison, ME, 1915 (Box 16, Folder 143)
- Textile Workers - Wilkes Barre, PA, 1919 (Box 16, Folder 144)
- United Textile Workers - Portage, PA, 1919 (Box 16, Folder 145)
- Amalgamated Textile Workers - N/A (Box 16, Folder 146)
- Textile Workers - Providence, RI, 1924 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Textile Workers - Pawtucket, RI, 1924-1926 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Textile Workers - Lebanon, NH, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Textile Workers - Greenville, NH, 1924 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Textile Workers - New York Mills, NY, 1925 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Textile Workers - Cohoes, NY, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Amalgamated Textile Workers - East Rutherford, NJ, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Textile Workers - Passaic, NJ, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Textile Workers - Paterson, NJ, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Textile Workers - Wale, MA, 1925 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Textile Workers - Worcester, MA, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Textile Workers - Fall River, MA, 1925 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Textile Workers - Lawrence, MA, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Textile Workers - Adams, MA, 1924 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Textile Workers - Shelton, CT, 1925 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- United Textile Workers - N/A, 1924 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Textile Workers - Alabama City, AL, 1925 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Amalgamated Textile Workers - Brockton, MA, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Textile Workers - Bridgeport, CT, 1925 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Textile Workers - Passaic, NJ, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Amalgamated Textile Workers - Arctic, RI, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Textile Workers - Reynoldsville, PA, 1919 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Textiles - Altoona, PA, 1918 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Textile Workers - Pittsfield, MA, 1925 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Textile Workers - New Bedford, MA, 1920-1927 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  1920, 1927
- Loomfixers - Chicopee, MA, 1922 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Textile Workers - Lawrence, MA, 1922 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Textile Employees - Clifton, NJ, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- United Textile Workers - Manchester, NH, 1918 (Box 17, Folder 29)
- Textile Workers - Worcester, MA, 1919 (Box 17, Folder 30)
- United Textile Workers - North Charlotte, NC, 1920 (Box 17, Folder 31)
- Textile Workers - Utica, NY, 1925 (Box 17, Folder 32)
- United Textile Workers - Cohoes, NY, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 33)
- United Textile Workers - Dunkirk, NY, 1918 (Box 17, Folder 34)
- Textile Workers - Woonsocket, RI, 1921 (Box 17, Folder 35)
- Textile Workers - Pascoag, RI, 1921 (Box 17, Folder 36)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Stockton, CA, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 37)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Denver, CO, 1918-1923 (Box 17, Folder 38)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Washington D.C., 1918-1923 (Box 17, Folder 39)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Springfield, MA, 1918 (Box 17, Folder 40)
- Scientific Projection Engineers - Chicago, IL, 1917 (Box 17, Folder 41)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Indianapolis, IN, 1918-1923 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  1918, 1919, 1923
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Savannah, GA, 1922 (Box 17, Folder 43)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - San Francisco, CA, 1917-1924 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  1917, 1919, 1923, 1924
- Theatrical Stage Employees - San Bernardino, CA, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 45)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Sacramento, CA, 1922 (Box 17, Folder 46)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Chicago, IL, 1916-1923 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  1916, 1919, 1923
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Oakland, CA, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 48)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Jacksonville, FL, 1922 (Box 17, Folder 49)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Crawfordsville, IN, 1913 (Box 17, Folder 50)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Ft. Wayne, IN, 1917-1923 (Box 17, Folder 51)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Indianapolis, IN, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 52)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Lowell, MA, 1921-1927 (Box 17, Folder 53)
  1921, 1924, 1927
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Davenport, IA, 1918-1926 (Box 17, Folder 54)
  1918, 1919, 1920, 1926
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Michigan City, IN, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 55)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Des Moines, IA, 1918 (Box 17, Folder 56)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Sioux City, IA, 1922 (Box 17, Folder 57)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Wichita, KS, 1917 (Box 17, Folder 58)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Haverhill, MA, 1922-1926 (Box 17, Folder 59)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - New Bedford, MA, 1928 (Box 17, Folder 60)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Spokane, WA, 1916-1919 (Box 17, Folder 61)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Sandusky, OH, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 62)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Astoria, OR, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 63)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Toledo, OH, 1919 (Box 17, Folder 64)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Lawton, OK, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 65)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Louisville, KY, 1918 (Box 17, Folder 66)
- Theatrical Stage Hands - Houston, TX, 1917 (Box 17, Folder 67)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Salt Lake City, UT, 1916 (Box 17, Folder 68)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Waltham, MA, 1922-1924 (Box 17, Folder 69)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Bay City, MI, 1922 (Box 17, Folder 70)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - S.S. Maine, MI, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 71)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Kansas City, MO, 1917-1923 (Box 17, Folder 72)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Buffalo, NY, 1917 (Box 17, Folder 73)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Elmira, NY, 1925 (Box 17, Folder 74)
- Theatrical Protective Union - New York, NY, 1918-1919 (Box 17, Folder 75)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Fall River, MA, 1918-1922 (Box 17, Folder 76)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Wheeling, WV, 1922-1924 (Box 17, Folder 77)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Providence, RI, 1918-1920 (Box 17, Folder 78)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Charleston, SC, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 79)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Milwaukee, WI, 1913-1919 (Box 17, Folder 80)
  1913, 1918, 1919
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Memphis, TN, 1917 (Box 17, Folder 81)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Boston, MA, 1918-1919 (Box 17, Folder 82)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Cincinnati, OH, 1916-1924 (Box 17, Folder 83)
  1916, 1918, 1922, 1923, 1924
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Florence, AL, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 84)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Reading, PA, 1922 (Box 17, Folder 85)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Pittsburgh, PA, 1919-1923 (Box 17, Folder 86)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Dayton, OH, 1918 (Box 17, Folder 87)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Birmingham, AL, 1922 (Box 17, Folder 88)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Mobile, AL, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 89)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Columbus, OH, 1919 (Box 17, Folder 90)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Cleveland, OH, 1914-1920 (Box 17, Folder 91)
  1914, 1920
- Theatrical Stage Employees - St. Paul, MN, 1917-1924 (Box 17, Folder 92)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - New Orleans, LA (Box 17, Folder 93)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Ft. Worth, TX, 1922-1927 (Box 17, Folder 94)
  1922, 1923, 1924, 1927
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Frederick, MD, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 95)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Dallas, TX, 1920-1923 (Box 17, Folder 96)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Seattle, WA, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 97)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Everett, WA, 1920 (Box 17, Folder 98)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Richmond, VA, 1922 (Box 17, Folder 99)
- Theatrical Stage Workers - San Antonio, TX, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 100)
- Cinematographers - New York, NY, 1922 (Box 17, Folder 101)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Detroit, MI, 1919-1924 (Box 17, Folder 102)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Philadelphia, PA, 1918 (Box 17, Folder 103)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Erie, PA, 1919 (Box 17, Folder 104)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Portland, OR, 1919-1923 (Box 17, Folder 105)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - N/A, 1920 (Box 17, Folder 106)
- Theatrical Stage Operators - San Mateo, CA, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 107)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - N/A, 1925 (Box 17, Folder 108)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Little Rock, AR, 1919-1920 (Box 17, Folder 109)
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Los Angeles, CA, 1918-1927 (Box 17, Folder 110)
  1918, 1927
- Theatrical Stage Employees - Detroit, MI, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 111)
- Timber Workers - International Falls, MN, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 112)
- Timber Workers - Seattle, WA, 1920 (Box 17, Folder 113)
- Timber Workers - Caryville, LA, 1919 (Box 17, Folder 114)
- Timber Workers - Deer River, MN, 1921-1923 (Box 17, Folder 115)
- Timber Workers - Port Arthur, TX, 1905 (Box 17, Folder 116)
- Timber Workers - District #1, 1919 (Box 17, Folder 117)
- Timber Workers - North Bend, OR, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 118)
- Timber Workers - Bend, OR, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 119)
- Trimmers - Memphis, TN, 1916-1924 (Box 17, Folder 120)
- Tobacco Workers - New Orleans, LA, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 121)
- Tobacco Workers - Detroit, MI, 1921 (Box 17, Folder 122)
- Tobacco Workers - Manchester, NH, 1914 (Box 17, Folder 123)
- Tobacco Stuffers - New Haven, CT, 1906 (Box 17, Folder 124)
- Tobacco Stuffers - Boston, MA, 1913 (Box 17, Folder 125)
- Tobacco Workers - Arecibo, PR, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 126)
- Tobacco Workers - St. Louis, MO, 1919 (Box 17, Folder 127)
- Tobacco Workers - New York, NY, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 128)
- Tunnel and Subway Construction - N/A (Box 17, Folder 129)
- Typographical - Long Beach, CA, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 130)
- Typographical - Miami, FL, 1925 (Box 17, Folder 131)
- Typographical - New York, NY, 1923-1926 (Box 17, Folder 132)
- Typographical - Lafayette, IN, 1922-1924 (Box 17, Folder 133)
- Typographical - Fresno, CA, 1921 (Box 17, Folder 134)
- Typographical - Cedar Rapids, IA (Box 17, Folder 135)
- Typographical - Memphis, TN, 1923-1926 (Box 17, Folder 136)
  1923, 1924, 1925, 1926
- Typographical - Scranton, PA, 1922-1924 (Box 17, Folder 137)
  1922, 1923, 1924
- Typographical - Abilene, KS, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 138)
- Typographical - Auburn, NY, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 139)
- Typographical - Madison, WI, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 140)
- Typographical - Scranton, PA, 1923-1927 (Box 17, Folder 141)
  1923, 1924, 1925, 1926, 1927
- Typographical - Washington, PA, 1925-1927 (Box 17, Folder 142)
- Typographical - Waukesha, WI, 1925 (Box 17, Folder 143)
- Typographical - Watertown, WI, 1924 (Box 17, Folder 144)
- Typographical - Cedar Rapids, IA, 1901-1926 (Box 17, Folder 145)
  1901, 1904, 1906, 1922, 1924, 1926
- Typographical - Elgin, IL, 1906-1926 (Box 17, Folder 146)
- Typographical - Galesburg, IL, 1924 (Box 17, Folder 147)
- Typographical - Herrin, IL, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 148)
- Typographical - Princeton, IN, 1924 (Box 17, Folder 149)
- Typographical - Columbus, GA, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 150)
- Typographical - Mascoutah, IL, 1906 (Box 17, Folder 151)
- Typographical - Decatur, IL, 1923-1927 (Box 17, Folder 152)
- Typographical - Chico, CA, 1923-1924 (Box 17, Folder 153)
- Typographical - Oakland, CA, 1924 (Box 17, Folder 154)
- Typographical - Marysville, CA, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 155)
- Newspaper Publishers - Indianapolis, IN, 1907-1917 (Box 17, Folder 156)
- Closed Shop United Typothetae and Franklin Clubs - N/A, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 157)
- Typographical - Grand Junction, CO, 1924 (Box 17, Folder 158)
- Typographical - Findlay, OH, 1924-1926 (Box 17, Folder 159)
- Typographical - Henderson, KY, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 160)
- Typographical - New York, NY, 1924-1926 (Box 17, Folder 161)
- Typographical - N/A, 1924-1926 (Box 17, Folder 162)
- Typographical - Cairo, IL, 1904-1905 (Box 17, Folder 163)
- Typographical - Pocatello, ID, 1924 (Box 17, Folder 164)
- Typographical - Boise, ID, 1924-1925 (Box 17, Folder 165)
- Typographical - Santa Cruz, CA, 1924 (Box 17, Folder 166)
- Typographical - Santa Rosa, CA, 1903 (Box 17, Folder 167)
- Typographical - Morris, IL, 1924 (Box 17, Folder 168)
- Typographical - San Pedro, CA, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 169)
- Typographical - Hartford, CT, 1901-1925 (Box 17, Folder 170)
  1901, 1925
- Typographical - Dayton, OH, 1929 (Box 17, Folder 171)
- Typographical - Saginaw, MI, 1901-1906 (Box 17, Folder 172)
  1901, 1906
- Typographical - Port Huron, MI, 1924 (Box 17, Folder 173)
- Typographical - Muskegon, MI, 1920 (Box 17, Folder 174)
- Typographical - Brockton, MA, 1923-1924 (Box 17, Folder 175)
- Typographical - Brainerd, MN, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 176)
- Typographical - Davenport, IA, 1922-1927 (Box 17, Folder 177)
  1922, 1924, 1927
- Typographical - Clinton, IA, 1924-1927 (Box 17, Folder 178)
- Typographical - Cedar Rapids, IA, 1922-1926 (Box 17, Folder 179)
- Typographical - New Orleans, LA, 1921 (Box 17, Folder 180)
- Typographical - Salem, OH, 1924 (Box 17, Folder 181)
- Typographical - Tulsa, OK, 1924 (Box 17, Folder 182)
- Typographical Newspapers - Norwich, NY, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 183)
- Typographical - N/A, 1914-1922 (Box 17, Folder 184)
  1914, 1916, 1918, 1922
- Typographical - Casper, WY, 1923-1925 (Box 17, Folder 185)
- Typographical - Chillicothe, OH, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 186)
- Typographical - St. Louis, MO, 1919-1923 (Box 17, Folder 187)
- Typographical - Huron, SD, 1924 (Box 17, Folder 188)
- Typographical - Orange, NJ, 1924-1925 (Box 17, Folder 189)
- Typographical - Ashland, KY, 1923-1926 (Box 17, Folder 190)
- Typographical - Leavenworth, KS, 1925 (Box 17, Folder 191)
- Typographical - Springfield, MO, 1922-1927 (Box 17, Folder 192)
  1922, 1924, 1925, 1927
- Typographical - Bay City, MI, 1923-1926 (Box 17, Folder 193)
- Typographical - Miles City, MT, 1920 (Box 17, Folder 194)
- Typographical - Lewiston, MT, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 195)
- Typographical - Dunellen, NJ, 1925 (Box 17, Folder 196)
- Typographical - Camden, NJ, 1922-1926 (Box 17, Folder 197)
  1922, 1924, 1925, 1926
- Typographical - Sacramento, CA, 1905-1924 (Box 17, Folder 198)
  1905, 1924
- Typographical - New York, NY, 1924-1926 (Box 17, Folder 199)
- Mailers - Cincinnati, OH, 1925-1927 (Box 17, Folder 200)
- Twisters - Bridgeport, CT, 1925 (Box 17, Folder 201)
- Upholsterers - New York, NY, 1923-1927 (Box 17, Folder 202)
- Upholsterers - N/A, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 203)
- Upholsterers - Los Angeles, CA, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 204)
- Upholsterers - Sacramento, CA, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 205)
- Upholsterers - San Francisco, CA, 1922 (Box 17, Folder 206)
- Upholsterers - Denver, CO, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 207)
- Carpet and Linoleum Mechanics - Boston, MA, 1926-1928 (Box 17, Folder 208)
- Upholsterers - Boston, MA, 1924-1926 (Box 17, Folder 209)
- Carpet Upholsterers - Washington D.C., 1924-1925 (Box 17, Folder 210)
- Upholsterers - Boston, MA, 1916 (Box 17, Folder 211)
- Upholsterers - Kansas City, MO, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 212)
- Upholsterers - St. Louis, MO, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 213)
- Upholsterers - Tacoma, WA, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 214)
- Upholsterers - Spokane, WA, 1924 (Box 17, Folder 215)
- Upholsterers - Philadelphia, PA, 1916-1927 (Box 17, Folder 216)
  1916, 1917, 1924, 1926, 1927
- Upholsterers - Oklahoma City, OK, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 217)
- Upholsterers - Dayton, OH, 1923 (Box 17, Folder 218)
- Upholsterers - Cleveland, OH, 1926 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Upholsterers - Cincinnati, OH, 1923 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Upholsterers - Syracuse, NY, 1923-1924 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Upholsterers - Rochester, NY, 1923 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Upholsterers - New York, NY, 1923-1926 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Upholsterers - Jamestown, NY, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Upholsterers - Trenton, NJ, 1925 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Upholsterers - New York, NY, 1923-1924 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Wire Weavers - N/A, 1918-1923 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  1918, 1920, 1923
- Wire Weavers - Appleton, WI, 1905 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Weavers - North Adams, MA, 1925 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Woolen Weavers - Tyngsboro, MA, 1923 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Weavers - Knoxville, TN, 1921 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Weavers - Riverport, RI, 1925 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Weavers - Philadelphia, PA, 1915-1923 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Weavers - Hightown, PA, 1916 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Weavers - Lawrence, MA, 1918 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Wood Carvers - Syracuse, NY, 1923-1924 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Wood Carvers - Cincinnati, OH, 1923 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Wood Carvers - Milwaukee, WI, 1923 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Wood Carvers - Boston, MA, 1921-1926 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Wood Carvers - Detroit, MI, 1925 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Wood Carvers - Baltimore, MD, 1923 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Wood Carvers - N/A, 1920-1925 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Wood Engravers - Chicago, IL, 1919-1927 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Wood Workers - San Francisco, CA, 1923 (Box 18, Folder 26)
- Wood Workers - Chattanooga, TN, 1918 (Box 18, Folder 27)
- RR Baggagemen, Brakemen, Yardmen - C St. PM & O, 1924 (Box 18, Folder 28)
- RR Baggagemen, Flagmen, Yardmen - Charleston Western Carolina, 1912-1924 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  1912, 1924
- RR Baggagemen, Brakemen, Flagmen, Yardmen, Switchmen - Louisville and Nashville, 1923-1924 (Box 18, Folder 30)
- Boilermakers - N/A, 1917-1920 (Box 18, Folder 31)
- RR Brakemen - Erie, PA, 1906 (Box 18, Folder 32)
- RR Baggagemen and Brakemen - Canadian National, 1926 (Box 18, Folder 33)
- RR Brakemen, Baggagemen, Yardmen - Norfolk and Western Railway, 1922-1924 (Box 18, Folder 34)
- RR Brakemen - South Pacific Lines, 1924 (Box 18, Folder 35)
- RR Brakemen, Baggagemen, Flagmen, Yardmen - Chicago and Alton, 1924 (Box 18, Folder 36)
- RR Clerks - Central of GA, 1921 (Box 18, Folder 37)
- RR Clerks, Freight Handlers, Station and Storage Employees - Chicago, IL, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 38)
- RR Clerks, Freight Handlers - Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 39)
- RR Clerks - Atlanta Coastline, 1922-1925 (Box 18, Folder 40)
- RR Clerks, Freight Handlers, Station Employees - Michigan Central, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 41)
- RR Clerks, Freight Handlers, Station Employees - Minnesota and St. Louis, 1921 (Box 18, Folder 42)
- RR Clerical and Station Employees - Louisville and Nashville, 1924-1925 (Box 18, Folder 43)
- RR Office Clerks - Minnesota and St. Louis, 1921 (Box 18, Folder 44)
- RR Clerks, Freight Handlers - Minneapolis and St. Paul, 1921 (Box 18, Folder 45)
- RR Clerks, Freight Handlers - Missouri, Kansas, Texas, 1922-1926 (Box 18, Folder 46)
- RR Clerks, Freight Handlers, Station Employees - Missouri Pacific, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 47)
- RR Clerks - Nashville, Chattanooga and St. Louis, 1921-1926 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  1921, 1924, 1926
- RR Clerical and Station Employees - Norfolk and Western Railway, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 49)
- RR Clerks, Freight Handlers - New York, New Haven and Hartford, 1923 (Box 18, Folder 50)
- RR Clerks - New York, New Jersey, 1916 (Box 18, Folder 51)
- RR Clerks, Station and Storehouse Employees - New York, New Haven and Hartford, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 52)
- RR Clerks - Southern Pacific, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 53)
- RR Clerks - Southern Pacific, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 54)
- RR Clerical and Office Forces - Philadelphia, PA, 1921 (Box 18, Folder 55)
- RR Clerks, Freight Handlers - N/A, 1921 (Box 18, Folder 56)
- RR Clerks - Seaboard Air Line, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 57)
- RR Clerks - St. Louis Southwestern, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 58)
- RR Clerks - Spokane, WA, 1925 (Box 18, Folder 59)
- RR Clerks - Chicago, Indianapolis, Louisville, 1921 (Box 18, Folder 60)
- RR Clerks - New York City, Chicago, St. Louis, 1924 (Box 18, Folder 61)
- RR Clerks, Freight Handlers - New York, NY, 1922-1923 (Box 18, Folder 62)
- RR Clerks - Norfolk, 1926 (Box 18, Folder 63)
- RR Clerks, Freight Handlers - Northern Pacific, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 64)
- RR Clerical Forces - Pennsylvania, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 65)
- RR Clerical Forces - Pennsylvania, 1921-1923 (Box 18, Folder 66)
- RR Clerks - Staten Island, 1923 (Box 18, Folder 67)
- RR Clerks - Bangor and Aroostook Railroad, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 68)
- RR Clerical Forces - International and Great Northern, 1921 (Box 18, Folder 69)
- RR Clerks - Kansas, Oklahoma and Coast, 1921 (Box 18, Folder 70)
- RR Clerks - Lake Erie and Western, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 71)
- RR Clerks, Freight Handlers - Southern Pacific, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 72)
- RR Clerks, Freight Handlers - Lake Erie and Western, 1921-1923 (Box 18, Folder 73)
- RR Clerks, Officers, Station Employees - Lehigh Valley, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 74)
- RR Clerks - Long Island Railroad, 1923 (Box 18, Folder 75)
- RR Clerical and Station Employees - Louisville ad Nashville, 1922-1925 (Box 18, Folder 76)
- RR Clerks, Freight Handlers - Maine Central, 1924-1927 (Box 18, Folder 77)
- RR Clerks, Freight Handlers - Western Pacific, 1923 (Box 18, Folder 78)
- RR Clerks - Wheeling and Lake Erie, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 79)
- RR Clerks, Freight Handlers - Mississippi Valley, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 80)
- RR Clerks, Freight Handlers - Wabash, 1923-1924 (Box 18, Folder 81)
- RR Freight Handlers - Minneapolis, MN, 1914 (Box 18, Folder 82)
- RR Clerks - Texas and Pacific, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 83)
- RR Clerks, Freight Handlers - Union Pacific, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 84)
- RR Clerks, Freight Handlers - Chicago and Alton, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 85)
- RR Clericals - Chesapeake and Ohio, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 86)
- RR Office and Station Employees - Central Vermont, 1921 (Box 18, Folder 87)
- RR Clerks - Central Vermont, 1921 (Box 18, Folder 88)
- RR Clerks, Freight Handlers - Colorado and Southern, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 89)
- RR Clerks, Freight Handlers - Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago and St. Louis, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 90)
- RR Clerks, Freight Handlers - Denver and Rio Grande Western, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 91)
- RR Clerks, Freight Handlers - Denver, CO, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 92)
- RR Clerks, Freight Handlers - Duluth, South Shore and Atlantic, 1921-1925 (Box 18, Folder 93)
- RR Clerks, Freight Handlers - Great Northern, 1920 (Box 18, Folder 94)
- RR Clerks, Freight Handlers - Illinois Central, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 95)
- RR Clerks - Boston and Maine, 1924 (Box 18, Folder 96)
- Electrical Workers - National, 1913-1923 (Box 18, Folder 97)
  1913, 1919, 1923
- RR Clerks, Freight Handlers - Chicago, Milwaukee and St. Paul, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 98)
- RR Clerks - Chicago and Eastern Illinois, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 99)
- RR Clerks, Freight Handlers - Chicago and North Western, 1923 (Box 18, Folder 100)
- RR Clerks - Chicago Great Western, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 101)
- RR Clerks - Chicago and Western Indiana, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 102)
- RR Clerks, Freight Handlers - Chicago, Burlington and Quincy, 1922-1924 (Box 18, Folder 103)
- RR Clerks - National, 1920 (Box 18, Folder 104)
- RR Employees - Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago and St. Louis, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 105)
- RR Clerical and Station Forces - Chicago, IL, 1925 (Box 18, Folder 106)
- RR Clerks - Chicago, St. Paul, Minneapolis, Omaha, 1923 (Box 18, Folder 107)
- RR Employees - Houston, TX, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 108)
- RR Clerks and Station Employees - Hocking Valley, 1922-1923 (Box 18, Folder 109)
- RR Clerks - Baltimore and Ohio, 1922-1925 (Box 18, Folder 110)
- RR Clerks - New Jersey, 1921 (Box 18, Folder 111)
- RR Clerks - Canadian National Railways, 1924 (Box 18, Folder 112)
- RR Clerks - Buffalo, Rochester, Pittsburgh, 1921 (Box 18, Folder 113)
- RR Clerical Employees - Boston and Maine, 1923-1926 (Box 18, Folder 114)
- RR Conductor, Baggagemen, Brakemen, Yardmen - Grand Trunk, 1917 (Box 18, Folder 115)